https://rcfdenver.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy describes how Rose Community Foundation uses and protects any information that you give the Foundation when you use this website. Rose Community Foundation is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should you be asked to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Foundation may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. Please check this page from time to time for changes.
Information collection and use
Rose Community Foundation may collect the following information:
•    Name, occupation, title, and organizational affiliation
•    Contact information including email address
•    Demographic information
•    Information related to preferences and interests
•    Other information relevant to surveys, grant applications and/or events
The Foundation uses this information to understand your needs and provide you with better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
•    Internal recordkeeping
•    Fulfillment of your requests for products and services
•    Improvement of our services
•    To contact you and to respond to your inquiries and requests for information
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Cookies
Rose Community Foundation uses cookies on this website. Cookies can enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that Rose Community Foundation does not have any control over other websites and is not responsible for the use and protection of any information that you give to other websites. You should exercise caution and review the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
Rose Community Foundation does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies or organizations. You can request that your information be deleted from our mailing list by emailing info@rcfdenver.org or by writing to the following address:
Rose Community Foundation
Communications Department: Privacy Policy Issues
4500 Cherry Creek Drive South, Suite 900
Denver, Colorado 80246
303.398.7400
If you have questions or suggestions about our privacy policy, please e-mail or write to us using one of the above addresses. In addition, if you believe that Rose Community Foundation holds any information about you that is incorrect or incomplete, please email or write to us as soon as possible, using one of the above addresses. Your information will be promptly corrected.
Effective date: June 1, 2013
